[Music]
what's the deal with airplane peanuts we
like and
love these types of people we like
high-profile
glossy
uh people that are are vapid and don't
have much going on in their heads but
think they
do like they are under the impression
they have big thoughts big big
thoughts like Megan and Harry I've
listened to both of them
talk Garden variety
retards both of them she's
hot he's Royal but Garden variety morons
either one of them I watched Megan and I
watched Harry they were using their
emotion to cover up the fact that they
were not
smart they were not too smart and they
were obviously it was an emotionally
charged
interview because they had just left the
country uh they had found out that the
royal family is uh racist which was
shocking um up until now they had only
thought that the the royal family uh had
murdered Harry's mother but upon finding
out that in addition to murdering har 's
mother they were also quite insensitive
on the topic of race no
good up until that point you said well
they're just an Illuminati death cult
that drink blood and live for a thousand
years and have murdered my fiance's
mother but we're going to give him a
shot and let's see how evolved they are
and it turns out they're not too evolved
and I watched the uh Oprah interview and
we talked about it on the show they're
just not bright so like many
people uh but they believe they are
bright be they say the right things
they're like there are so many people in
the world
without yes there is so many people in
the world without which is why we have
to come to Los Angeles and live in a
beautiful mansion with round the-clock
security we got to get a deal at Netflix
and make documentaries about people that
are
[__] that's what it is they want to be
on Netflix and make documentaries about
people with cleft pallets she's a
Hollywood actress means she's ambition
she has ambition um actors are stupid
people they're not smart very few of
them are intelligent and the ones that
are intelligent are much much older
young actors are and we know many of
them they're insanely dumb to where it's
noticeable have you ever been with
someone who's so dumb it's noticeable
where you look at someone else as if to
be in disbelief at what this person is
doing if you had lunch with Megan Markle
you'd be stunned and out dumb Shew not
cuz she's black cuz I wouldn't think she
was black if I looked at her because
she's an actress who is on the show
Suits okay she's an actress Harry is an
idiot he's an idiot for two reasons
number one he signed up to fight in the
Afghanistan war that was a dumb move
you're a [__] Prince what are you
doing that [__] for number two
I know it's heroic I guess after 911 but
I think he signed up years after that
that's hilarious and number two I he
still believe in this dumb story that
the paparazzi killed his mom maybe he
doesn't maybe just so she gets him to
leave his family she goes she goes why
do we want to stay here and I get it I'm
for them why do we want to stay here
they're racist the weather sucks the
food [__] let's go to La we'll eat sushi
by the pool every day and we'll make
documentaries about people with cleft
pallets he goes well is is it when their
face is all yes she goes and then every
now and then we'll fly one of them over
we'll clean up their face and we'll take
them to Disneyland but we got to get out
of the UK and we got to come to the US
and we're going to go on Oprah and then
every idiot in America but he's but
they're mad at rich people not our kind
of rich people she goes I'm kind of
black and you're an idiot so you just
and you're willing to be emasculated so
you just sit there and eat your own [__]
on TV I'll tell Oprah that they were
chasing me around the Royal Palace with
nooses and then Netflix will open up a
suitcase full of money and we'll go do
documentaries about kids with cleft
pallets is it LO where their lip is in
their nose yes yes just Google it Harry
so that's what went on watching people
fawn over them we like royalty we love
it we like Rich PE stop pretending you
don't like rich people stop pre the
people that tweet about Marxism all day
then talk about how much they love the
Real Housewives you just can't quit it
and nobody is a realer housewife than
Megan marle who married this Ginger
[__] and took him out of his racist
family so that they could live in
Beverly Hills or wherever the [__] they
live and make documentaries about people
without
hands on
Netflix Netflix by the way who's
committed to just giving these people
anything they want whenever they want
they're making a cartoon what is the
cartoon about it's called Pearl yes it's
about a young girl who is inspired by
influential women in history and counts
David fernish and Liz Garbus among its
executive
producers uh yeah I guess that's it the
Advent of a 12-year-old girl who's
inspired by influential women in history
the series currently in development it's
all the information we have that's it uh
she's on a journey of self-discovery as
she tries to overcome life's daily
challenges says well that sounds great
good for her man do you know how many
actresses that do a show like suits just
get thrown out out in the street true
afterwards Megan Markle parl that into a
[__] royal wedding and then a year in
or a couple years in said [__] that [__]
and left and I'm not saying the royal
family was not racist to her I'm sure
they were but that also didn't start
when she got there an exciting tale that
weaves together fantasy and history
Pearl focuses on a young girl who learns
to step into her own power when she
embarks on a heroic adventure and meets
important women from history along the
way so you know what this is going to be
like Pearl's going to go back you know
there's going to be a scene where
Pearl's like who are you my name is
Harriet Harriet who Harriet Tubman we
got a railroad and you go oh my God this
is the Underground Railroad yes it
is this is so amazing I can't believe it
you're so brave and strong yes I am
child but I'm not nearly as brave and
strong as Megan Marco who's that she was
an actress on suits it's a TV show
yeah she married Prince Harry you know
the son of that woman they killed in a
in the thing in the tunnel and they said
the Press did it but you you know was
good cuz she was going to marry DOD alen
he was Muslim it's a whole thing is oil
Saudi Arabia whatever you got to follow
Cynthia McKinny on Twitter what anyway
I'm just
saying yes I'm where's cyy mckin at the
Met Gala by the way that all she did was
talk up at 911 all day where is she
where is she where's
she well here's what I'm saying child
I'm saying it I may be brave but the
bravest person ever is Megan Marco thank
you
I'm excited for that show that is the
message from the government if you don't
have symptoms and you've tested negative
uh you're not out of the woods so by the
way that's fun for the anxiety hopefully
nobody has anxiety one in three La
residents have been infected by Corona
virus it's a new estimate it's a neelen
rating we think this amount of people
are watching Jersey Shore we don't know
but if you have anxiety this has been
great how's in the last year been nicer
remember when we all cared about mental
health all of a sudden that went out the
window when the media every other day is
going are you do you feel good guess
what did you test negative guess what
you got it
[__] it's real and it sucks but here's
the other thing this is a little a
message for the people that have
survived it because I've had
enough I really have had enough now with
I was in a yard yesterday two people in
the yard had had Co they hijacked the
entire event which was not really an
event it was just a a hang
they hijacked it to
discuss how they both beat Co how bad it
was and how no one in the history of the
world will ever understand the struggles
that they went through not AIDS not
cancer not those [__] with ALS nobody
will understand how hard it is to be Co
I go I haven't had it I said I've been
being relatively careful I said I got
very sick and March I had all of the
symptoms I had tightness to the chest I
had chills I woke up in the middle of
the night I couldn't really leave the
bed I was exhausted I could make it from
my bed to my couch maybe I lost smell I
don't really know but I know that taste
was all [__] up I could barely eat it
took me three and a half weeks to get my
things back and then they look at you
and they go no you didn't have it you
would know if you had it this doesn't
even feel organic it's a bioweapon that
you do battle with and they're literally
do
like Cobra Kai moves in the yard about
how Co they're like you think you're
good and then it hits you from the side
and then you double over and then you
have to kick and you have to hit you
again and I'm like what and then I'm
like well other people get really sick
you know my friend's mother had
pancreatic cancer she fought that for 10
years and they're like [__] that [__] I
had Co you don't understand it's a
bioweapon they act like they defeated
the Chinese military with this you can't
even get a word in edgewise with these
people you can't say that other people
get sick people die of cancer is cancer
not a thing anymore what about AIDS with
these [__] people lesions all over
the how about ebola I mean these [__]
cuns will go to Africa people bleeding
out of their eyes there's lepers on the
thing they go you don't know about Co I
couldn't taste my hot dog you don't know
about Co it's just a
bioweapon Ebola is just one of those
cute diseases that comes from the nature
it's not a weapon I beat a weapon so it
just gets a little it gets a little
frustrating what is that it frust
frustrating FR is doesn't it sound
better as frustrate I do like that it's
quicker this whole thing we know how bad
Co is we know how much it [__] people
up I've had friends tell me how how how
how bad it has been for them both
physically and mentally I understand
that Dan for example my opener who's had
it is now occasionally tired so I get I
get it the point is I don't know why I
haven't gotten this but here's what I
will tell you I know that it's really
bad and vicious it when people get it in
a bad and vicious way but is one of the
symptoms that you have to discuss it for
seven months afterwards is there any let
up here because truly when you bring up
any other disease they look at you like
you don't get it and I'm like well what
about ALS where you get diagnosed and
you literally become a puddle and then
die within two years they go they go no
still no not a bioweapon they go you
don't get they go you don't get it this
is made in a lab and I beat it and then
they tell you they're like this is how I
beat it I sat in the room and I just
went I'm going to beat it I'm going to
beat it I'm going to beat it and they're
like you don't even understand the what
you go through the mental Fitness you
have to have and I'm like yeah okay but
again my friend's mother
fought a death sentence pancreatic
cancer for 10 years it's unheard of the
woman was out doing marches she was
raising money there are people that
overcome horrible conditions there are
people born with horrible conditions
okay okay so this idea that the only
thing in the world that anyone the the
mark of a man is that he beat Kover the
mark of a man the mark of a soldier
they're acting and I know it's bad but
the way that they're talking and acting
makes me feel so much less sympathetic
for them because it's getting obnoxious
it's obnoxious to tell a group of people
that somehow they're less than because
they didn't beat what they're calling a
Chinese bioweapon these are the people
by the way that have had it they're like
China tried to take Hong Kong with this
bioweapon I beat it but it's tough how
about ALS get ALS up that's a walking in
the park apparently cuz of uh Co let's
get ALS
up muscle cramps tight and stiff muscles
slur in nasal speech difficulty chewing
or swallowing which which ends up no
chewing or swallowing okay literally
what it does is it immobilizes you and
it's insane how bad it is
okay difficulty swallowing drooling lack
of restraint mild cognitive impairment
severe constipation unintentional weight
loss shortness of breath difficulty
raising your foot so you bring this up
to these people and they go dude you
don't even get it you don't even [__]
get it dude this is like lab made it's
something else something different it's
just annoying it's just annoying and
it's got to stop I know it's bad but
it's got to
stop life is a Pandora's box of horror
okay people have all kinds of problems
some people's problem s are greater than
others some people have to go through
horrible things okay I understand that
this can be an an insane life-changing
event for people it could be a horrible
thing it could kill them it could kill
me I've been open and honest about that
but what we don't want to do is annoy
people to death as well by by pretending
that you are the only thing that matters
and that the things that you've gone
through are the only things that anyone
should ever take
seriously that everybody body else in
this country that's suffering because we
have an opioid epidemic or because their
jobs have evaporated or because they
don't have health insurance okay or that
they work all week for [__] wages and
nobody cares about them and they have to
[__] navigate this world without any
help from anybody those people should
all shut the [__] up because you hadn't
got sick I had Co okay I don't want to
hear about your hemorrhagic fever your
Ebola boo
I just did a little fake business now
you know that I do this a lot of the
audience don't know that I do I do fake
business I call up Realtors all day when
I'm bored and I pretend I'm a realtor
and that my client is very interested in
their property and I asked them lots of
questions about their property I just
did it with the commercial property on
Palm County drive he said hey this is
Tim uh I have a client of investor
that's really interested in the property
what are we looking at per square foot
and what are some of the local
restrictions we should know about and
you know these whole things they they go
into this whole thing they go well you
know they don't want a coffee shop in
there because Starbucks there's a
competing business Clause so Starbucks
doesn't want a coffee shop this is how
the corporate takeover of America is by
the way because when Starbucks moves
into an area they go yeah we don't need
we don't want some independent coffee
shop opening not all areas but a lot of
them we don't need somebody slinging
lattes for less than we are so the guy
goes well there's a Sprint stores we
can't do a competing business blah BL
blah and we we talked about it there's a
lot of parking behind I said thank you I
said I have an investor but he's very
concerned about you know the competing
business clause and everything like that
I was on the phone with this guy for
about 10 minutes and he say to me oh Tim
that's cruel their time has value no it
doesn't and I will continue to do fake
business because I enjoy I like doing
fake business it's one of my favorite
things to do I like to call people and I
like to lie about who I am and and and
what I do and then I like to see how
they conduct business because on their
end they're conducting real business I'm
conducting fake business now never the
two shall meet we've gotten to the point
where I was we're almost one of my
clients who doesn't exist was almost
going to put an offer on a house this
was last week I was I've been on the
phone with this realtor for like 45
minutes three times in a row I've had to
block her finally she doesn't know what
happened sometimes I have to block the
people because fake business gets very
intense fake business people start
drawing up contracts I mean she was
calling appraiser she was going to have
inspections done you know I was
representing a very motivated overseas
client
now sadly that client died of Corona
virus before we could go see the
property that's not my fault and I tried
to explain that to her but she was kind
of confused and started saying oh this
you know blah blah blah are you real is
this real cops FBI whatever blah blah
blah blocked
blocked I'm helping train these
professionals do you understand yes or
yes I by calling them people need
practice so this sh schmuck over there
on pal Canyon I did use my real name by
the way like this is Tim Dylan and
sometimes I make up a firm name
sometimes I use a real firm name
sometimes I just say this is Tim Dey
with Futures he goes what I go Futures
investment he goes okay just go okay you
go yeah all right I go yeah you got a
commercial listing on pal Canyon on the
corner I'm wondering what we're looking
at price per square foot what's the
parking in the area like what's the
competing business Clause what any local
restrictions you should know about I
have a team of investors that are
looking to expand into this area many of
them uh sometimes it's a franchise
sometimes not but I'm just you know it's
an investment group they're very
interested they love the visibility of
the loc oh he goes it's a great location
so they love the visibility of the loc
and see right there we're beginning to
do fake business because then he goes to
his wife and he goes hey I just got a
call from a guy that may be interested
in this and then he tells his secretary
and then he tells his partner so I'm in
I'm in and I'll give him a follow-up
call later tonight I'll have 10 more
bullet point questions before I bring my
investor now I do this now a lot of
people I was explaining to someone at
dinner that I did I do this and they go
it's horrible I said why I'm doing fake
business they go why I said I like doing
it because I don't have a real estate
license and I can't do real business but
I at least can do fake business they
said that's pretty sick I said maybe
you're sick because I want Realtors to
get the best professional I want you're
golf a lot right when you golf when you
golf every day are you better at it yes
absolutely now that doesn't me now even
that includes going to a driving range
sure right correct right sometimes I see
golfers swing clubs in their backyard
helps helps doesn't matter if it's real
or fake what matters is that this guy's
going through the moat the next guy to
call him might be real but I'm going to
beat that guy out I'm going to do a
competitive
offer hello hey Adam Tim Dylan how are
you we spoke about the property on Palm
Canyon a few minutes
ago yeah hey Tim how's it going good
buddy how are you I wanted to know if
there's a list of the the competing
Clause uh my clients asking me if
there's a list of businesses whether
it's Starbucks Sprint things like that
that we could kind of figure out what
the restrictions are just so I could
kind of email that to them because he
wants to show it to the the his
investors if that's possible also is
there a way they can get out to see the
proper property maybe later in the
week yeah yeah I live about four minutes
from it so not too
difficult that and um uh I will just go
to the center right now and send you a
quick list of all the businesses that I
I would appreciate that let me ask you a
question too how long has this property
been on the market I have I haven't
looked it up
yet yeah I've been marketing it for
maybe I think we I just signed it like
right when Co hit and then I delayed it
for like two or three months so I'd say
maybe like two or three months now okay
and what before you had it was it was it
sitting there for a while or no they
always like to know these
things yeah I don't I know Banner
Mattress was there up until recently
okay um so I know there's a mattress
like right across the street yeah I saw
that is this would this be a fiveyear
lease or what what are we what are they
looking for in terms of
commitment yeah really just depends on
the the tenant and the rate things like
that obviously the longer the the
commitment the better we can do on the
rate um but um you know I think they're
open right now okay and I and I imagine
I imagine they're open to some form of
negoti
at you know given the
climate of course of course okay well I
appreciate that I have we're here to do
deals yeah me too but I mean me too it's
a little wild out there you know are you
guys mainly commercial you do any
residential um I do a bit of both okay
good yeah you got to be kind of a
generalist out here I I agree yeah a lot
of people are starting to get interested
in this area and I think it's because
you know LA's had a lot of problems and
a lot of my a lot of my clients I do
business primarily in in in Los Angeles
and a lot of people are starting to look
at this area and um you know a lot of
them are are are excited about maybe
jumping
into uh something here you know because
the high season I imagine it's what
January through through
June uh yeah January through April is
our high high season right um but pretty
much like right now like September
through April um you know so we have
kind we kind of have like a shoulder
mid-season
which is September through December
right and then January through April
just crushes and then Coachella is
obviously and Stage coacher in April and
that kind of you know and we have
Memorial Day Weekend July 4th even
during the summer we do pretty well of
course I appreciate that well listen I
have you guys I have your website I'm
going to shoot you an email um just
again introducing myself and then if you
could just get me a list of some of
those competing business Clauses just so
I can show it to them and uh hopefully
they'll get out to see it sometime uh
next week you know they're they're super
interested one of them lives out here in
Rancho and uh they pass it all the time
so they they had me just kind of reach
out to you and see what was going on but
they're pretty motivated and again I
think it's all about you know how
restrictive those Clauses
are yeah I I think they're going to be
pretty flexible so I'll shoot you the
businesses yes and uh we'll see if we
can do something okay I appreciate it
Adam thanks a lot for your time all
right thank you so I do it's fake
business and I'm doing it well I'm doing
it well let's be honest I'm doing it
well I'm protecting the interest of my
clients I'm protect am I not am I not
protecting the interest of my clients
when I conduct fake
business my fake clients are important
and they need to be
protected I want them to have the
maximum amount of freedom in any given
situation you understand start doing
fake business will change your life I'm
telling you that right now start doing
it no one can St you don't need a
license you just need a phone and a
computer and you can start doing fake
business set up a fake email address I
have one start doing fake business right
now it's the gateway to real business
I've done nothing you understand I do
not get be reviews on Airbnb because I
treat people with
respect now let's
describe let's describe some of the
issues number one I went I was told was
going to a luxury compound in Joshua
Tree luxury means something very
specific to me okay it doesn't mean
necessarily stylized High concept and
artistic it means luxury it means fluffy
couches and nice carpets luxury I feel
luxurious you understand yes um we went
to a a nice thing in Joshua Tree which
is the place where all people in the
tech industry go to take mushrooms and
people that work for ice go and have you
know to take DMT and figure out how to
build stronger cages to put kids in you
know it's great it's for people having
Revelations so we go to Joshua Tree
which is really just it's a litter box
for drug addicts let's be honest it's a
litter box for drug addicts and I know
that a lot of people like it but that's
what it is and that's who you are so we
get into the house the house the the
furniture in the house is like it's all
it's all of course these are two white
women I believe they're lesbians I don't
want to say that they're lesbians I
don't know but their names are stupid
like one of them name is Mila it's like
it's a stupid name you're a ridiculous
person okay you accuse me of breaking a
cactus how do you even do that you goofy
[__] shut the [__] up okay you slob so
I walk into your [__] house which you
can't even sit on the [__] FR I got
fat people here they're 400b how are
they going to sit on your cowhide chair
that's a little thin thing of [__]
leather what are we supposed to do this
guy's 900 lb what are we going to do
here okay every piece of furniture can't
sodomize the guest you have to have some
[__] chair that works like an actual
[__] chair throw a bean bag in there
okay not everybody's a 90 foot 90 PB
lesbian on iasa that can perch on a
[__] bird cage for the whole night
okay you freaks listen the [__] up
talking to you people are going to rent
your house in are actual people that
need actual Furniture to actually sit
not everything's a [__] trip to
hyperspace space there's actual 3D
reality that some of us have to [__]
live
in so we went
there and we do nothing to the furniture
we we literally don't damage any of the
furniture they have these kitchen stools
that are concrete
slabs Mila MAA we work so hard for the
shut up get a job there are concrete
slab kitchen chairs high top kitchen
chairs okay that are like art pieces
these are not chairs and then they have
little stools that are made out of what
what was that like hollowed out so like
marble or yeah the marble petrified wood
petrified wood or I don't know what it
was tall though it's yeah it's a little
stool that you're supposed to sit it's a
tiny little table with where your ass
can't even fit on this small little
thing of wood you have to sit on and eat
I don't even know what right so they
just want you doing drugs do you walk in
as a big martar in a pestl there and
they're like just crush it up just crush
it up and do it get it into the blood
and that's fine listen I get it you want
to go Char t t the shrimps but some
people want to have a nice meal there we
treated that house like it had never
been treated it with wholesome American
food we went to van in the desert and we
got burgers and bushes baked beans and
we cooked baked beans and yes beans
explode when they're hot
yeah whose fault is that I didn't come
up with the idea for the Bean they
explode when and then we wanted uh
Gorton's fish we got the Gorton's fish
which is very nice the breaded pre-
breeded Gorton's fish and some tartis
sauce so we so baked beans Gorton's fish
with tartar sauce cheeseburgers and then
seven pints of ice cream so we could try
yeah just have a little ice cream
testing and we left a few
dishes in the sink in the sink a pot of
exploded beans yeah an extra tarar sauce
I didn't even use that I said you can
use um some ice cream I mean the smell
of the house was fish and bean yeah but
that's not my fault you could have a
cleaning crew she's like the cleaning
crew complained what what is it my fat
maid over there probably complaining but
it's like well why are they complaining
they're supposed to be cleaning their
job is to clean okay so this [__] then
texts me she goes our cleaning crew had
a hard attack LOL so I'm like okay and
then she goes but please give us a good
review so we stay on Airbnb so here's
the deal with Airbnb we review each
other we don't know what we've said if
you're going to come reach out to me and
ask me for good review and acknowledge
that the cleaning crew is like oh we got
to wash some dishes I'm like okay
they're not mad we didn't do anything
there's some dishes in the sink but it
is what it is I paid a $400 cleaning fee
you stupid [__] jonan mil you [__]
pigs I'll burn your [__] house down
by the way anyway I texted them that I
texted them I was going to burn their
house down and I sent them a gift of The
Simpsons house burning I'm like I know
where your house is they're like are you
threatening me I'm like let's just see
what happens I'm like stay safe out
there you stupid desert dikes anyway so
I responded to her by saying no one
broke anything your house sucks cuz she
said I was a bad guas and then and then
people are like did this really happen I
like yeah it really
happened I said the f the furniture is
unusable you're not artist your home is
wildly overpriced true you beg me for
good rating and then trash me the
cleaning crew complained about cleaning
who's your cleaning cre
there were some dishes that is all I
don't really care about your reviewers I
don't rent up my home to Strangers Like
An animal good luck with everything in
the future the place is a dump and it
looks like it was furnished by drug
addicts which I imagine you are please
get the help you need if you want me to
take you to an AA meeting or an NA
meeting I will go to IKEA get some
actual Furniture which hopefully you can
afford not everything has to be an art
piece and feel free to use the tartar
sauce I left behind later Pig and that's
what I wrote to them on Airbnb and no
response and then I and I and then I
sent a few the could have been
considered quasi threatening messages
but they were not threats they were an
art piece like your furniture they're
not meant to be sat on or taken
literally I was doing an art piece you
see it was all a
metaphor and didn't anger it angered me
because she [__] on me publicly on
Airbnb which anyone can see truly and
now I look like the bad guy I look like
the bad guy [__] you we didn't do
anything dishes were in the sink the hot
tub wasn't hot you already paid $400 for
a clean if we're not supposed to eat the
Gordon's fish why would they sell it at
the
supermarket I'm not getting fresh fish I
trust a Gorton's fisherman yeah and it's
a lovely if you've ever had a Gorton's
they're lovely very good and then the
mcor MC tardar sauce goes very well with
it it pairs very well I thought so I'm
sorry I wasn't doing speedballs in your
bathroom like the rest of your
guests you [__] pigs
you've done nothing but create a [__]
satanic Vortex for people to sin and I
didn't take part in it I made bowls of
baked
beans I I will not Toler I will not
tolerate being disparaged publicly like
that and this good man does he he did
nothing wrong he slept in a room where
the sun hit him directly in the face as
soon as it came up yeah there were no
[__] curtains yeah cuz curtains are
too basic for these [__] hoes and I
hope they hear this by the way I hope
someone in your garbage life shows you
this podcast you are nothing do you
understand me you clowns look at your
Airbnb picture you're you pose with your
[__] dogs you're clowns you are not
interesting and you are not an artist
you are failures and you are drug
addicts and I'm telling you right now if
you had any clue the holy hell that was
about to rain down on you you would
[__] run you would head you would run
out into the desert and sacrifice
yourself because every day I swear to
Christ every [__] day I wake up and I
think about how to destroy you in that
[__] hole and I'll figure it out and see
this is what I mean about the cops can't
call me out on this because it's my
right to kind of vent these frustrations
and I can't because they can't knock on
my door and say hey did you say you
going to kill these two dikes and joshu
Retreat I can't this is what I mean do
you see in real time I'm proving my
point from the beginning of the show
that's why the show is entertaining and
it's informative because the reality is
we're all having these thoughts all the
time because what I really want to do is
gas these two in their house and watch
them just I want to watch them [__]
climb over their shitty ART housee
furniture and get to the [__] door
and just just they can't get any breath
and then fall and then just walk in and
I want to piss on their corpses but I'm
not going to do that I'm not going to do
that I'm just going to talk about it do
you understand the difference I put that
up and I said today is my birthday I
want to thank my my parents for all
their support this is what you created
enjoy it and my
aunt wrote a comment and the comment
let's not find it let's not find it yeah
you're right and the comment was and my
cousin sent me the comment my the
comment was the saddest part is that you
have your grandfather's name and you
don't care at all and and you care
nothing about his legacy very very nasty
comment very very nasty comment and you
know me I hate to bring family drama on
the show I hate that that you know I
don't do it we can get this down I I
really don't do it okay uh my aunt
Kathleen by the way okay uh comes from
me on
Instagram brings up my grandfather and
insults me on the day of my birth
now let's get something straight you bum
[__] didn't you fake a drug
overdose didn't you fake a suicide
attempt I keenly remember you faking
that you overdosed on drugs and you were
taken to a hospital in an ambulance in
front of your mother who had just dealt
with Grandpa's death what part of
Grandpa's Legacy were you honoring with
that behavior what part of it do you
remember that I remember you going to a
hospital and then having the entire
family go worried about you not me but
other people cuz I know what you're up
to you clown [__] they went to the
hospital and said what drugs is she on
doctor and the doctor goes there are no
drugs in her system she literally
pretended to be unconscious so then an
ambulance went to the home put her in it
and drove her to the hospital scaring
her mother half to death Grandpa's
Legacy okay what part of Grandpa's
Legacy were you thinking about when you
took his money for law school and then
never practiced law and were fired
multiple times by multiple law firms all
over Long Island because you're mentally
ill forcing uh your father to set up a
pretend law office for you in your base
man that you pretend to be a lawyer in
you added phone line to the house to
pretend to be an
attorney what part of the legacy is that
what part of the legacy is borrowing
money from your more successful brothers
and sisters and not paying any of it
back while you sit around the house
doing perco set and drinking white wine
what part of the legacy is that are you
honoring his days as a
carpenter is that what you're honoring
by S around and getting junked up on the
couch pretending to OD and by the way
the lives you live you don't even have
to pretend okay you can't even do that
right so I'm just wondering why you
would bring up my grandfather where I
have all the respect in the world for a
legendary character patriarch of an
amazing family Rose from poverty did all
these things why come on my Instagram
and say anything negative and and bring
up a guy who every day with your life
and your choic is where is his legacy in
mind Kathleen and I know you watch this
okay in between reading Q drops and
letting Fox News broil your already
Viking and addled brain
okay it's the wrong day Kathleen I'm the
wrong one you know that I blocked you on
the family uh I I got a new phone to get
the family [__] group text cuz you
kept texting people about all the dishes
they have to do when they come to the
family parties [__] no one's coming
anymore no one cares I don't want to be
near you you should be in a padded room
how my mother is in an asylum and you
have somehow escaped it is beyond me and
it's beyond everybody you are a disgrace
drug addict potentially closeted lesbian
you've never moved out of the house
nobody respects you you are a pedophile
probably you are gross around kids
nobody wants you [__] taking baths
with their [__] kids you're a [__]
weirdo they got to watch you like
[__] Epstein so don't keep my name
out of your mouth okay pedophile drug
addict this is the fake business
mug and the fake business mug uh is is
not on sale anymore is it it's still for
sale oh it is for sale till the 28th
yeah so you don't work you don't have a
family you steal money you fake drug
overdoses is you're a moral degenerate
you you you have no respect for people
you drive wedges in between people and
the family and you attack successful
people in the family my grandfather did
none of those things he was a devoutly
religious incredibly generous brilliant
hard worker who raised an entire family
you are the exact opposite of all of
those things all of those things okay
every one of them I blocked you I got a
new phone to get out of the group chat
because I didn't want to deal with your
constant terrorism or updating me like
hey uh little Tom got his license who
hey who gives a [__] dummy get a job get
a [__] job I have a job why don't you
get a job stop worrying about who got
their license nobody wants you near
their
family you [__] freak where's your
man [__] where's your woman where's
anything
what are you doing I mean let let's get
real I mean this is a woman who does
nothing but but attack attack attack and
by the way [__] my f and I like some of
them but and then my aunt goes like this
uh she goes like this she
goes she goes oh you know if I bump
she's told this to somebody else goes if
I bumped into him I'd really give him a
piece of my mind how are you going to
bump into me [__] I don't live in your
kitchen okay you you've never left
you've never left home I'm in Malibu ho
how am I going to bump into you okay
buying tan packs at the local CVS for
your Barren childless vagina how would
we ever bump heads together keep my name
out of your mouth
scumbag you're a degenerate you're a
moral de this isn't even a podcast
anymore I'm talking directly to you you
are a failure and a moral degenerate
okay
c pig from a sketch a few years ago on
my chest is a funny dumb joke you my
friend are a
disgusting nightmare that nobody wants
to be around you're a thief you've
stolen people's money haven't you
Kathleen you've stolen money haven't you
you know you have where's the money
Kathleen did you take it you took all
the money didn't you and then you go cry
and some people the family be like
you're being too hard on her [__] you
too hey [__] you too you think I give a
[__] about any of you [__] you [__] I
have a family okay it's Joe Rogan and
Candace Owens my mother and father give
a [__] about you [__] clowns go do a
[__] Irish step dance I don't give a
[__] this [__] is out of her [__] M
you are out of your mind bringing my
grandfather my Instagram trying to
trying to knock me like that it's a
shitty thing to do especially from you
who's
accomplished zero in your entire [__]
life and I I would be worried that you'd
sue me but you don't know how to
practice law you're not a real lawyer
are you because you work from a basement
and you have pretend clients you set up
a Care Bear you had from when you were
[__] nine and you still have CU you
never left your house and you go hello
Mr Care Bear did you have a dewe well
let's look at your
you're a clown [__] no one takes you
seriously you should be getting
electroshock therapy that's kind of how
I wanted to start off the show okay
that's it for this video honorable
mention to the Gates of Hell In the
Night of the beating those weren't
videotaped so couldn't really include
them in this video but here's one more
rant for you go follow Joker on
Instagram we have these free stickers
for everyone that DMS us go follow us
dude there's 7,000 people following on
Instagram and 56,000 following on
YouTube that doesn't make sense we're
posting very similar stuff on Instagram
than we are on YouTube get over there I
don't know how to get you guys over
there this is my rant this is my only
rant go follow us get these free
stickers just DM us your address and you
get these stickers you can put them
anywhere you want do you have stuff that
is ugly look it makes it better you can
put them on your friends you can put
them on stop signs water bottles laptops
your [__] it doesn't matter go get
these stickers go follow us on Instagram
that's it have a great day
[Music]
oh